if you've been curious about the Scarlet
Darkness brand here's my experience with
them early this year I found my wing
photo used in one of their ads without
permission I emailed them they said
their designer got the photo off
Pinterest we worked it out and they sent
me some cute stuff like this pink
dress but a month or so later I saw
another ad using that same design again
without
permission I emailed again and they
responded insisting that this was their
original
design I opened their file in photosop
found my original photo that they had
previously used in that ad put it on top
and adjusted the transparency settings
with an overlay filter and y'all this is
traced at least in that newer ad not a
whole lot of the wings were visible so
whatever and I'm not made of money so
I'm still going to wear this stuff and
it works well with my wings they're easy
to put on by myself and the bodices are
decent they have a lot of boning even
though it's plastic and I like that
there is a zipper on the side to easily
get in and out and this bodice goes
really well with this green chiffon
pirate
shirt mostly I want them to know that
they're not fooling anybody and those
wings were obviously traced from my
photo
so I hope they learn from this because
their stuff is cute and it is Affordable
but I don't know about the rest of their
ethics as a
company however I do like that their
dresses have pockets so there you go